Sam B. Hall, Jr. Papers, Inclusive: 1943-2005, undated Bulk: 1976-1985
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Events, 1975-2005, undated; 5
  - General, 1975-2005, undated; 1
    - Texarkana Meeting with Congressmen Anthony, Roemer, Watkins, Hall and Secretary Hightower, 1984 February 21 (Box 288, Folder 7)
    - Overton Rotary Club, 1984 February 24 (Box 288, Folder 8)
    - Doris, James Farmer Reception, 1984 March 23 (Box 288, Folder 9)
    - East Texas State University Young Democratic Texas Forum, 1984 March 26 (Box 288, Folder 10)
    - Governmental Affairs Institute, 1984 March 29 (Box 288, Folder 11)
    - Kimberly-Clark Dedication, Paris, 1984 March 30 (Box 288, Folder 12)
    - J.L. Jones Retirement Party, Gilmer, 1984 April 1 (Box 288, Folder 13)
    - Harrison County Retired Teachers, 1984 April 4 (Box 288, Folder 14)
    - Marshall Chapter of the Business and Professional Womens Clubs, Legislative Seminar, 1984 April 7 (Box 288, Folder 15)
    - Ralph M. Hall Dinner, 1984 April 16 (Box 288, Folder 16)
    - Texarkana Noon Lions Club, 1984 April 16 (Box 288, Folder 17)
    - Jacksonville High School, 1984 April 17 (Box 288, Folder 18)
    - National Association of Railroad Passengers Southern Region, Ginocchio Hotel, 1984 April 20 (Box 288, Folder 19)
    - Caddo Pharmaceutical Association of Mt. Pleasant, 1984 April 20 (Box 288, Folder 20)
    - Clarksville, Dedication of Housing Limits, 1984 April 21 (Box 288, Folder 21)
    - Bogota, Rosalie Lodge #527, 1984 April 21 (Box 288, Folder 22)
    - Northeast Texas Educators, 1984 April 25 (Box 288, Folder 23)
    - Gilmer High School, 1984 April 26 (Box 288, Folder 24)
    - Carthage Lions Club, 1984 April 26 (Box 288, Folder 25)
    - San Augustine Chamber of Commerce, 1984 April 27 (Box 288, Folder 26)
    - Town Hall Series, Spring Street Community Center, 1984 April 28 (Box 288, Folder 27)
    - National Association of Broadcasters, 1984 April 30 (Box 288, Folder 28)
    - HUDCO Annual Older Americans Day, 1984 May 13 (Box 288, Folder 29)
    - Carlisle High School, 1984 May 20 (Box 289, Folder 1)
    - ABA Forum Committee on Air and Space Law, Orlando, Florida, 1984 May 23-24 (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - Internment of an Unknown Service Man from Vietnam ERA, 1984 May 25 (Box 289, Folder 3)
    - National Cable Television Association, 1984 June 4 (Box 289, Folder 4)
    - Marshall District Office, 1984 July 17 (Box 289, Folder 5)
    - Texarkana Chamber of Commerce Breakfast, 1984 August 1 (Box 289, Folder 6)
    - LVN Award Day Banquet, 1984 August 10 (Box 289, Folder 7)
    - Red River County Farm Bureau, 1984 August 15 (Box 289, Folder 8)
    - Linden Lions Club, 1984 August 16 (Box 289, Folder 9)
    - Texarkana District Office, 1984 August 17 (Box 289, Folder 10)
    - Sulphur Springs, 1984 August 21 (Box 289, Folder 11)
    - Agriculture Export Commission, 1984 October 9 (Box 289, Folder 12)
    - Texarkana District Office, 1984 October 12 (Box 289, Folder 13)
    - Texarkana Chamber of Commerce Annual Membership Banquet, 1984 October 12 (Box 289, Folder 14)
    - Shelby County Farm Bureau, 1984 October 13 (Box 289, Folder 15)
    - First Methodist Church of Atlanta, 1984 October 14 (Box 289, Folder 16)
    - Mt. Pleasant Rotary Club, 1984 October 16 (Box 289, Folder 17)
    - International Credit Union Day Banquet, Texarkana, 1984 October 17 (Box 289, Folder 18)
    - Harrison County Retired Teachers Association, 1984 October 18 (Box 290, Folder 1)
    - Clarksville Chamber of Commerce Reception, 1984 October 18 (Box 290, Folder 2)
    - Detroit Flagpole Dedication and Reception, 1984 October 18 (Box 290, Folder 3)
    - Cooper Luncheon, 1984 October 18 (Box 290, Folder 4)
    - Patterson Library, 1984 October 18 (Box 290, Folder 5)
    - Tatum Elementary School, Dedication, 1984 October 21 (Box 290, Folder 6)
    - Harrison County Farm Bureau, 1984 October 22 (Box 290, Folder 7)
    - Marshall Civic Center, Dedication, 1984 October 23 (Box 290, Folder 8)
    - Greenville E-Systems, 1984 October 26 (Box 290, Folder 9)
    - Cooper Lake Ceremony, 1984 October 27 (Box 290, Folder 10)
    - Pleasant Grove Independent School District, Groundbreaking Ceremony, 1984 October 29 (Box 290, Folder 11)
    - Henderson County Farm Bureau, 1984 October 30 (Box 290, Folder 12)
    - Lon Morris College, Jacksonville, 1984 October 30 (Box 290, Folder 13)
    - Andrew Gibbs Reception, 1984 November 1 (Box 290, Folder 14)
    - Jacksonville Chamber of Commerce, 1984 November 2 (Box 290, Folder 15)
    - Northeast Texas Community College, 1984 November 3 (Box 290, Folder 16)
    - Red River Intern Training Center Bar-B-Q, 1984 November 5 (Box 290, Folder 17)
    - National Association of Retired Federal Employees, Texarkana Chapter 300, 1984 November 5 (Box 290, Folder 18)
    - Marshall High School, 1984 November 5 (Box 290, Folder 19)
    - Billy E. Reed, American Engineering Process, 1984 November 15 (Box 290, Folder 20)
    - Overton Rotary Club, 1984 November 30 (Box 290, Folder 21)
    - Marshall Optimist Club, 1984 November 30 (Box 290, Folder 22)
    - Marion/Camp County Coop Dedication of Special Education Center, 1984 December 18 (Box 290, Folder 23)
    - Paris, 1984 December 18 (Box 290, Folder 24)
    - Marshall Office, 1984 December 19 (Box 290, Folder 25)
    - Tour of Red River and Lone Star Depots, 1984 December 27 (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - Breakfast Club, Marshall, 1984 December 29 (Box 291, Folder 2)
    - Democratic Study Group, Special Report, 1985 January 27 (Box 291, Folder 3)
    - Henderson, District 19 VFW Convention, 1985 February 10 (Box 291, Folder 4)
    - Marshall Advisory Council, 1985 February 11 (Box 291, Folder 5)
    - Red River Valley Association, 1985 February 12 (Box 291, Folder 6)
    - Paris, Rotary Club and Transportation Committee of Chamber of Commerce, 1985 February 15 (Box 291, Folder 7)
    - Lone Star Chamber of Commerce, 1985 February 16 (Box 291, Folder 8)
    - Williamsburg, Judicial Conference, 1985 March 8-10 (Box 291, Folder 9)
    - Gilmer, Groundbreaking Ceremonies for Upshur County Justice Center, 1985 March 23 (Box 291, Folder 10)
    - Awards, Certificate of Appreciation, Marshall BPW Club, 1985 April 7 (Box 291, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Ernest, Sons of Republic of Texas, 1985 April 12-13 (Box 291, Folder 12)
    - Marshall High School Class Reunion 45th anniversary, 1985 August 24-25 (Box 291, Folder 13)
    - Sam B. Hall Reception, Clarksville, TX, 1985 October 18 (Box 291, Folder 14)
    - Shultz, George, Speech, America and the Struggle for Freedom., 1985 February 22 (Box 291, Folder 15)
    - Rural Housing, Statement, Morton J. Schussheim, 1985 February 26 (Box 291, Folder 16)
    - Transcript from Swearing in Ceremony as Federal Judge, 1985 May 25 (Box 291, Folder 17)
    - Presentation of the Portrait of the Honorable Sam B. Hall, Jr. to the United States District Court, Eastern District of Texas, 1991 November 15 (Box 291, Folder 18)
    - Ceremony Naming the Sam B. Hall, Jr. Federal Building and United States Courthouse, Marshall, TX, 1995 May 29 (Box 291, Folder 19)
    - Book Signing at East Texas Baptist University, 2005 July 9 (Box 291, Folder 20)
    - Texas Electric Co-operative’s, Inc. luncheon, 1980 February 29-July 21 (Box 291, Folder 21)
    - Reception in Honey Grove, TX, undated (Box 292, Folder 1)
  - Administrative, 1976-1985, undated; 2
    - Appointment Book, Black “At A Glance”, 1976 (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Appointment Book, Blue “Day Minder”, 1976 (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - Appointment Cards, 1976 (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 292, Folder 6)
    - Guestbook, Coffee for Sam Hall, Jr. Loyd Wilson Room, First National Bank, New Boston, TX, 1976 April 3 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Guestbook, Sam B. Hall, Jr. M.C., 1976-1978 (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - Guestbook, Paris District Office, 1976-1984 (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Appointment Book, Black “Babcock and Wilcox”, 1977 (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Appointment Book, Red “Appointment Diary”, 1977 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Appointment Book, Brown “Desk Master Diary”, 1977 (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Appointment Cards (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Appointment Cards (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 294, Folder 3)
    - Sam B. Hall, Jr., 1977 May 19-1980 January 2 (Box 294, Folder 4)
    - Appointment Book, January-February Loose leaf, 1978 (Box 294, Folder 5)
    - Appointment Book, Black “Day at a Glance”, 1978 (Box 294, Folder 6)
    - Appointment Cards (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 294, Folder 7)
    - Appointment Cards (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - Appointment Book, Brown Cathedrals, 1979 (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - Appointment Book, Brown “Week at a Glance”, 1979 (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - Appointment Cards (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 295, Folder 4)
    - Appointment Cards (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - Appointment Book, Tan “Week at a Glance”, 1980 (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - Appointment Book, Brown Parks, 1980 (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - Appointment Cards (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - Appointment Cards (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - Sam B. Hall, Jr. M.C., 1978 June 19-1980 October 2 (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Guestbook, Sam B. Hall, Jr. Congressional Office, 1980 October 7-1983 March 8 (Box 296, Folder 5)
    - Sam B. Hall, Jr., 1980 January 3-1984 January 4 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Speech file, 1980-1981 (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Speech file, 1980-1981 (Box 297, Folder 3)
    - Appointment Book, Black Planning Calendar for Legislators, 1981 (Box 297, Folder 4)
    - Appointment Book, White “Week at a Glance”, 1981 (Box 297, Folder 5)
    - Appointment Book, White “Week at a Glance”, 1982 (Box 297, Folder 6)
    - Appointment Book, White “Week at a Glance” A, 1983 (Box 297, Folder 7)
    - Appointment Book, White “Week at a Glance” B, 1983 (Box 298, Folder 1)
    - Congressman Sam B. Hall, Jr., 1983 March 8-1985 May 14 (Box 298, Folder 2)
    - Appointment Book, White “Week at a Glance” A, 1984 (Box 298, Folder 3)
    - Appointment Book, White “Week at a Glance” B, 1984 (Box 298, Folder 4)
    - Guestbook, Congressman Sam B. Hall, Jr. Marshall District Office, 1984 January 4-1985 May 28 (Box 298, Folder 5)
    - Guestbook, Marshall Awards Banquet in Honor of Sam B. Hall, Jr., 1984 February 13 (Box 298, Folder 6)
    - Installation Ceremony for the Honorable Sam B. Hall, Jr. Marshall, Tx, 1985 May 28 (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - Awards. Blank, undated (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - Media in 1st Congressional District, Newspaper, Weekly and Daily, Radio Stations, undated (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘A’, undated (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - Rolodex, Armed Service Academies, undated (Box 299, Folder 5)
    - Rolodex, Department of Agriculture, undated (Box 299, Folder 6)
    - Rolodex, Animal and Plant Health Inspection Service, undated (Box 299, Folder 7)
    - Rolodex, Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, undated (Box 299, Folder 8)
    - Rolodex, Forest Service, undated (Box 299, Folder 9)
    - Rolodex, Rural Electrification Administration, undated (Box 299, Folder 10)
    - Rolodex, Soil Conservation Service, undated (Box 299, Folder 11)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘B’, undated (Box 299, Folder 12)
    - Rolodex, Bicentennial, undated (Box 299, Folder 13)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘C’, undated (Box 299, Folder 14)
    - Rolodex, U.S. Civil Service Commission, undated (Box 299, Folder 15)
    - Rolodex, Community Service Administration, undated (Box 299, Folder 16)
    - Rolodex, Department of Commerce, undated (Box 299, Folder 17)
    - Rolodex, Census Bureau, undated (Box 299, Folder 18)
    - Rolodex, Economic Development Administration, undated (Box 299, Folder 19)
    - Rolodex, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, undated (Box 299, Folder 20)
    - Rolodex, Patent Office, undated (Box 299, Folder 21)
    - Rolodex, Community Action Resource Services, undated (Box 299, Folder 22)
    - Rolodex, Consumer Affairs, undated (Box 299, Folder 23)
    - Rolodex, Corps of Engineers, undated (Box 299, Folder 24)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘D’, undated (Box 299, Folder 25)
    - Rolodex, Department of Defense, undated (Box 299, Folder 26)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘E’, undated (Box 299, Folder 27)
    - Rolodex, Electric Cooperatives, undated (Box 299, Folder 28)
    - Rolodex, Energy Research and Development Administration, undated (Box 299, Folder 29)
    - Rolodex, Environmental Protection Agency, undated (Box 299, Folder 30)
    - Rolodex, Equal Employment Opportunities Commission, undated (Box 299, Folder 31)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘F’, undated (Box 299, Folder 32)
    - Rolodex, Farm Credit Administration, undated (Box 299, Folder 33)
    - Rolodex, Federal communications commission, undated (Box 299, Folder 34)
    - Rolodex, Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, undated (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - Rolodex, Federal Energy Administration, undated (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - Rolodex, Federal Home Loan Bank Board, undated (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - Rolodex, Federal Power Commission, undated (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - Rolodex, Federal Reserve System, undated (Box 300, Folder 5)
    - Rolodex, Federal Trade Commission, undated (Box 300, Folder 6)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘G’, undated (Box 300, Folder 7)
    - Rolodex, General Services Administration, undated (Box 300, Folder 8)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘H’, undated (Box 300, Folder 9)
    - Rolodex, Department of Health and Human Services, undated (Box 300, Folder 10)
    - Rolodex, Office of Education, undated (Box 300, Folder 11)
    - Rolodex, Public Health Service, undated (Box 300, Folder 12)
    - Rolodex, Department of Housing and Urban Development, undated (Box 300, Folder 13)
    - Rolodex, Federal Disaster Assistance Administration, undated (Box 300, Folder 14)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘I’, undated (Box 300, Folder 15)
    - Rolodex, Department of Interior, undated (Box 300, Folder 16)
    - Rolodex, U.S. Fish and Wild Life Service, undated (Box 300, Folder 17)
    - Rolodex, National Park Service, undated (Box 300, Folder 18)
    - Rolodex, Interstate Commerce Commission, undated (Box 300, Folder 19)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘J’, undated (Box 300, Folder 20)
    - Rolodex, Department of Justice, undated (Box 300, Folder 21)
    - Rolodex, FBI, undated (Box 300, Folder 22)
    - Rolodex, Immigration and Naturalization Service, undated (Box 300, Folder 23)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘K’, undated (Box 300, Folder 24)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘L’, undated (Box 300, Folder 25)
    - Rolodex, Law Enforcement Assistance Administration, undated (Box 300, Folder 26)
    - Rolodex, Department of Labor, undated (Box 300, Folder 27)
    - Rolodex, Occupational Safety and Health Administration, undated (Box 300, Folder 28)
    - Rolodex, Library of Congress, undated (Box 300, Folder 29)
    - Rolodex, Congressional Research service, undated (Box 300, Folder 30)
    - Rolodex, Copyright Office, undated (Box 300, Folder 31)
    - Rolodex, Letter ’M’, undated (Box 300, Folder 32)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘N’, undated (Box 300, Folder 33)
    - Rolodex, National Labor Relations Board, undated (Box 300, Folder 34)
    - Rolodex, Office of Economic Opportunity, undated (Box 300, Folder 35)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘P’, undated (Box 300, Folder 36)
    - Rolodex, U.S. Postal Service, undated (Box 300, Folder 37)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘R’, undated (Box 300, Folder 38)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘S’, undated (Box 300, Folder 39)
    - Rolodex, Small Business Administration, undated (Box 300, Folder 40)
    - Rolodex, State, undated (Box 300, Folder 41)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘T’, undated (Box 300, Folder 42)
    - Rolodex, Telephone Companies, undated (Box 300, Folder 43)
    - Rolodex, Texas, undated (Box 300, Folder 44)
    - Rolodex, Department of Transportation, undated (Box 300, Folder 45)
    - Rolodex, Federal Aviation Administration, undated (Box 300, Folder 46)
    - Rolodex, Federal Highway Administration, undated (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - Rolodex, Urban Mass Transit Administration, undated (Box 301, Folder 2)
    - Rolodex, Department of Treasury, undated (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - Rolodex, U.S. Customs Service, undated (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - Rolodex, Internal Revenue Service, undated (Box 301, Folder 5)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘U’, undated (Box 301, Folder 6)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘V’, undated (Box 301, Folder 7)
    - Rolodex, Water Supply Corporations, undated (Box 301, Folder 8)
    - Rolodex, Letter ‘W’, undated (Box 301, Folder 9)
    - Rolodex, White House, undated (Box 301, Folder 10)
  - Invitations, 1976-1993; 3
    - Invitations (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 301, Folder 11)
    - Invitations (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 301, Folder 12)
    - Invitations (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 301, Folder 13)
    - April-May, 1978 (Box 301, Folder 14)
    - September, 1978 (Box 301, Folder 15)
    - Collections of Invitations, 1979 (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - Invitations, 1979 (Box 302, Folder 2)
    - March (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 302, Folder 3)
    - March (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 302, Folder 4)
    - July-August, 1979 (Box 302, Folder 5)
    - October (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 302, Folder 6)
    - October (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 302, Folder 7)
    - November, 1979 (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - Invitations, December, 1979 (Box 303, Folder 2)
    - American Ex- POW’s Dinner with Framed Certificate, 1980 December 12 (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - January, 1981 (Box 303, Folder 4)
    - February, 1981 (Box 303, Folder 5)
    - March, 1981 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - April, 1981 (Box 304, Folder 2)
    - May (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - May (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - June (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 305, Folder 2)
    - June (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 305, Folder 3)
    - Hearings on Nomination of Judge Sandra Day O’Connor, 1981 August 27 (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - July, 1981 (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - September, 1981 (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - October (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - October (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 306, Folder 2)
    - November, 1981 (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - December, 1981 (Box 306, Folder 4)
    - Invitation (Accepted but said yes in Marshall), December, 1981 (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - January, 1982 (Box 306, Folder 6)
    - February, 1982 (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - March, 1982 (Box 307, Folder 1)
    - April (1 of 3), 1982 (Box 307, Folder 2)
    - April (2 of 3), 1982 (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - April (3 of 3), 1982 (Box 307, Folder 4)
    - December, 1983 (Box 307, Folder 5)
    - Invitation, February (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 307, Folder 6)
    - Invitation, February (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 307, Folder 7)
    - Invitations, March (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 308, Folder 1)
    - Invitations, March (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 308, Folder 2)
    - Invitations, April (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 308, Folder 3)
    - Invitations, April (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 308, Folder 4)
    - April, 1984 (Box 308, Folder 5)
    - May (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 308, Folder 6)
    - May (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 309, Folder 1)
    - June, 1984 (Box 309, Folder 2)
    - July-August, 1984 (Box 309, Folder 3)
    - September (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 309, Folder 4)
    - September (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 309, Folder 5)
    - 50th Presidential Inauguration (Ronald Reagan) (1 of 2), 1985 January 21 (Box 310, Folder 1)
    - 50th Presidential Inauguration (Ronald Reagan) (2 of 2), 1985 January 21 (Box 310, Folder 2)
    - 52nd Presidential Inauguration (William Clinton), 1993 January 20 (Box 310, Folder 3)
    - May, undated (Box 310, Folder 4)
- Executive, 1976-1982; 6
  The Executive files include campaign and inaugural materials for President Jimmy Carter as well as materials regarding conferences and international conflicts. The bulk of the materials cover President Ronald Reagan’s Economic Recovery Plan of 1981. Sam Hall received correspondence from his constituents for almost one year regarding the plan. Files are arranged chronologically 1976-1982 and are in good condition.
  - Carter-Mondale Campaign Materials, 1976 (Box 310, Folder 5)
  - Inauguration, Personal Requests, 1976-1977 (Box 310, Folder 6)
  - White House Conference on Small Business, 1978 (Box 310, Folder 7)
  - Proposal for Natural Resources Reorganization, 1979 April (Box 310, Folder 8)
  - Iran Hostages, Soviet Invasion of Afghanistan, 1979-1980 (Box 310, Folder 9)
  - Reagan Address, Economic Recovery, 1981 February (Box 310, Folder 10)
  - Regulatory Relief, Background (1 of 3), 1981 February (Box 310, Folder 11)
  - Regulatory Relief, Background (2 of 3), 1981 June (Box 310, Folder 12)
  - Regulatory Relief, Background (3 of 3), 1981 August- December (Box 310, Folder 13)
  - Regulatory Relief, Conference Report, H.J. Res. 357, 1981 (Box 311, Folder 1)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, February, 1981 (Box 311, Folder 2)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, March (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 311, Folder 3)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, March (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, April (1 of 6), 1981 (Box 311, Folder 5)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, April (2 of 6), 1981 (Box 311, Folder 6)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, April (3 of 6), 1981 (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, April (4 of 6), 1981 (Box 312, Folder 2)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, April (5 of 6), 1981 (Box 312, Folder 3)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, April (6 of 6), 1981 (Box 312, Folder 4)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, May (1 of 5), 1981 (Box 312, Folder 5)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, May (2 of 5), 1981 (Box 312, Folder 6)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, May (3 of 5), 1981 (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, May (4 of 5), 1981 (Box 313, Folder 2)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, May (5 of 5), 1981 (Box 313, Folder 3)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, June (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 313, Folder 4)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, June (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 313, Folder 5)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, July (1 of 3), 1981 (Box 313, Folder 6)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, July (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 313, Folder 7)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, July (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 314, Folder 1)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, August (1 of 4), 1981 (Box 314, Folder 2)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, August (2 of 4), 1981 (Box 314, Folder 3)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, August (3 of 4), 1981 (Box 314, Folder 4)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, August (4 of 4), 1981 (Box 314, Folder 5)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, September, 1981 (Box 314, Folder 6)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, October (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 314, Folder 7)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, October (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 315, Folder 1)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, November, 1981 (Box 315, Folder 2)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, December (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 315, Folder 3)
  - Regulatory Relief, Correspondence, December (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 315, Folder 4)
  - State of the Union Address, Reagan, 1982 January (Box 315, Folder 5)
- Judicial, 1980-1994; 7
  Judicial Files reflect two parts of Sam Hall’s career. The Appropriations subseries covers budget issues Hall dealt with as part of his committee work, while all other subseries, Cases, Opinions and Rulings, and Scripts, reflect his work as U.S. District Court Judge of the Eastern District of Texas. Items in this series are dated 1980-1994 and in good condition. Detailed information can be found prior to each subseries.
  - Appropriations, 1980; 1
    The Appropriations series is the contents of a binder labeled “The Judiciary, Justification for 1980 Appropriations Estimates.” It is the Congressional Submission for Fiscal Year 1980 Budget Estimates. Divider tabs have been retained signifying each part of the budget addressed; folders have been named according to these divisions. Folders are in original order and follow the table of contents.